--- 1. Register QA Hospital ---
Registered QA Hospital ID: 16

--- 2. Register QA Donors ---
Registered QA Near A+
Registered QA Far Critical A+
Registered QA Universal Donor O-

--- 3. Testing Standard Request (10km, A+, High) ---
Standard request matched 2 donors.
 - QA Near A+ (1.55 km)
 - QA Universal Donor O- (3.11 km)

--- 4. Testing Critical Request (20km, A+, Critical) ---
Critical request matched 0 donors.

--- 5. Testing Cooldown (Immediate Repeat) ---
Cooldown check matched 0 donors. (Expected fewer or 0)
